movienuke.com 2016-02-15

# Best Latest Hot Video Clips

MovieNuke recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use www.MovieNuke.com (collectively or individually "Users") value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the MovieNuke Website. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the MovieNuke Terms of Service. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. 

BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE WEBSITE), YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. MovieNuke reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the Website following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. 

If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Website. 

## The Information MovieNuke Collects

MovieNuke does **not** knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Website from any person.   
\- Cookies: MovieNuke may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Website, You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some functionality of our Website may be impaired if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.   
\- Log File: When you use the MovieNuke WebSite, our servers record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring, landing, exit pages and URLs, operating system type, number of clicks, domain names, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request. 

## How is the information being used?

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by MovieNuke. We use the information to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. The information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures, as determined by MovieNuke in good faith. 

## Third Party Ad Servers

MovieNuke allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the MovieNuke Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the MovieNuke Website. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not MovieNuke's. 

## Youth Restrictions

If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner 

## Non-U.S. Users

The Website is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the MovieNuke Website from a jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.
